Mandeep Kaur

Front End Developer and IT Coordinator

OBJECTIVE

To use my expert problem solving, attention to detail, knowledge and communication skills that I have learnt from my Graduate Certificate in Software Development, my IT Coordinator and customer services job roles for developing responsive websites and products with collaboration of team members.

CONTACT

Address 320 Livingston View NE,

Calgary, T3P 0Z9

Mob: (437) 228-2597

GitHub: https://github.com/mandeep72332

 $email: mandeepkhablan@gmail.com \\ LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/mandeep-kaur-658365173/$

EDUCATION

Full Stack Certification(In Progress)

July 2022 – ongoing

Udemy Boot Camp

Enterprise Software Development Program, Postgraduate. May 2019

Humber College, Toronto, ON

Master of Computer Applications

Punjab Technical University, India

April 2014

Bachelor of Computer Applications

April 2011

Punjab University, India

EMPLOYMENT

IT Coordinator August 2021 – Present

Insights - IT Contractor with City of Calgary

- Proactively engage with clients by attending telephone calls, greeting customers, communication through emails, phone and Teams with the customers, deployers, Project Move Co-ordinator of City of Calgary
- Responsible for scheduling Net New equipment, hardware Installs, Scheduling IT Moves, Coordinate with Office Moves and prepare documents, presentations and correspondence.
- Meet Service Level Agreements, use of Remedy Software to update tickets, coordinate Courier delivery of equipment,
- Apply Best Practices (ITIL), based methodology to Problem Management, Incident Management & Change Management disciplines.
- Escalation to the team lead and liaison with third party vendor or client as required.
- Follow documentation including Knowledge Base articles and Technical Alerts.
- Participate & Darticipate amp; contribute to service improvement plans.
- Completion within the SLA and Update Remedy tickets and Asset information providing accurate and complete documentation of work performed
- Assist in training team members on process and technology
- Coordinate meetings, prepare and distribute agendas, record and distribute meeting minutes and monitor and action items to
 ensure completion.

Office Administrator Officer

June 2019 – April 2020

Bestway Education

- Proactively engage with clients by attending telephone calls, greeting customers, communication through emails with the
 agents and college admission teams.
- Responsibility to create Offer letters, Letter of Acceptance, check admission eligibility requirements of international students
- Update the database of student's college data like student's details, tuition fee etc.
- Focus on education and demonstration, leverage technology to deliver a memorable client experience, drive solutions and retain business.
- Presciently take ownership of resolving and preventing client's problems related to eligibility criteria, accommodations, pickup etc.
- Provide administrative support through records management

Office Assistant Dec. 2018 – May 2019

New Homes & Condos Presentation Centre, Brampton

- Manage telephone calls, including screening incoming calls and corresponding with buyers, sellers, tenants and vendors.
- Manage emails in professional manner, reply to the daily queries, sending promotional emails to existing clients.
- Greet the visiting clients, answer their queries and arrange the meeting with Sales Representatives.
- Maintain high level of confidentiality and trust with secure information.
- Prepare Agreements of Purchase and Sale, Tarion papers, Lease Agreements, Listing Agreements; related Amendments.
- Send Commission Invoices to Vendors, follow up on the commission cheques, receive the invoices and forward to accounting
 department.
- Arrange appraisal appointments, inspection appointments, showing appointments with adequate notice; proper communication with Tenants/Owners.

RELEVANT PROJECT WORK

Tindog: Sept. 2022

I have created this website while practicing my Full Stack Developer Course at Udemy. This website is responsive and it helps to find pets. It also includes different Pricing options and testimonials as well. I used Carousels, cards, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS and JavaScript for creating this website.

Capstone Project "PassVault":

May 2019

PassVault is a password manager that securely stores your passwords and personal information in a secure vault. PassVault will auto fill your login credentials as you visit apps and sites. You have to create and remember a PassVault master password, and PassVault will autofill logins for you. PassVault remembers your passwords for you and keep you from away from struggling with frustrating password resets. I have used HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, Express, MongoDB etc.

Online Movie Booking: -

April 2019

Technologies: Front-End (Asp.NET MVC) and Back-End (SQL SERVER)

This project has two modules like user and admin for adding the movies in tables and viewing the details of movies. Both user and admin can login with their login credentials saved in tables. I used the SQL Server to create the tables and to store the data of movies.

LANGUAGES KNOWN FLUENTLY

English, Hindi, Punjabi

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Troubleshooting: Ability to troubleshoot hardware, software, and peripheral devices including: printers,

network issues, operating systems.

Software: MS Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access), SQL Server Management

Studio, Power BI

Operating Systems:Windows 7/8/XP/10, Mac OSDatabase:SQL Server, Oracle, MongoDB

Web Technology: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, React, ASP.net MVC, C, Node.js, Express.

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- Accountability, flexibility and professionalism in performing all duties
- Demonstrated interpersonal and communication (both oral and written) skills.
- Displayed sound decision-making skills and the ability to resolve conflicts sensitively and respectfully
- Experience and success in working in a culturally diverse environment.
- A strong team player with the ability to build collaborative working relationships.
- Client-focused is tenacious about finding and delivering quality results for our clients.
- Results-oriented is resourceful and proactive; and knows that delivering on promises is the basis of relationship health and longevity.
- The ability to prioritize a high volume of work in a fast paced environment.